export const plans = [
    {
    name: "Basic",
    price: "$99",
    features: [
        "Reach 300 Influencers",
        "Analytics",
        "1 Active Campaign",
        "Weekly Reporting",
        "10% Media Charges",
        "Priority E-mail Support"
    ]
    },
    {
    name: "Starter",
    price: "$299",
    features: [
        "Reach 500 Influencers",
        "Analytics",
        "5 Active Campaigns",
        "Bi-Weekly Reporting",
        "7% Media Charges",
        "Priority E-mail Support"
    ]
    },
    {
    name: "Enterprise",
    price: "$499",
    features: [
        "Reach 1000 Influencers",
        "Analytics",
        "10 Active Campaigns",
        "Daily Reporting",
        "5% Media Charges",
        "Dedicated Account Manager"
    ]
    }
]
  
export const web3faq = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "1. How does vitamin i work?",
    answer: "Vitamin i enhances the body's immune system by boosting the production of white blood cells. It also acts as an antioxidant, helping to protect cells from damage caused by free radicals."
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "2. How do I get paid?",
    answer: "Payment transactions are conducted directly on our website. We utilize ERC20 and BEP20 addresses for payment processing. Upon order completion, you will have the option to select your preferred chain and effortlessly receive your funds."
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "3. How much does it cost?",
    answer: "The cost varies depending on the specific service or product you are interested in. Please refer to our pricing page for detailed information."
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "4. Is my payment guaranteed?",
    answer: "Yes, your payment is guaranteed. We ensure secure transactions through our platform and provide a refund policy to protect your investment."
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "5. What platforms does Vitamin i support?",
    answer: "Vitamin i supports a variety of platforms including Windows, macOS, iOS, Android, and various web browsers. This ensures compatibility and accessibility across different devices."
  }
]

export const brandfaq = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "1. How does vitamin i work? (Brands)",
    answer: "Vitamin i enhances the body's immune system by boosting the production of white blood cells. It also acts as an antioxidant, helping to protect cells from damage caused by free radicals."
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "2. How do I get paid?",
    answer: "Payment transactions are conducted directly on our website. We utilize ERC20 and BEP20 addresses for payment processing. Upon order completion, you will have the option to select your preferred chain and effortlessly receive your funds."
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "3. How much does it cost?",
    answer: "The cost varies depending on the specific service or product you are interested in. Please refer to our pricing page for detailed information."
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "4. Is my payment guaranteed?",
    answer: "Yes, your payment is guaranteed. We ensure secure transactions through our platform and provide a refund policy to protect your investment."
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "5. What platforms does Vitamin i support?",
    answer: "Vitamin i supports a variety of platforms including Windows, macOS, iOS, Android, and various web browsers. This ensures compatibility and accessibility across different devices."
  }
]

export const platForms = [
  {
    icon: "./platforms/BINANCE.svg",
  },
  {
    icon: "./platforms/LEDGER.svg",
  },
  {
    icon: "./platforms/CoinEx.svg",
  }, 
  {
    icon: "./platforms/Zebpay.svg",
  },
  {
    icon: "./platforms/Beldex.svg",
  }
]

export const features = [
  {
    title: "Uncover the Perfect Influencers",
    description: "Efficiently discover influencers who align with your brand’s values",
    icon: "./okay.svg"
  },
  {
    title: "Seamless Connection and Collaboration",
    description: "Effortlessly connect and collaborate with influencers",
    icon: "./okay.svg"
  },
  {
    title: "Efficiency and Effectiveness Reporting",
    description: "Track & optimize the effectiveness of campaigns",
    icon: "./okay.svg"
  },
  {
    title: "Convenient Crypto Payments and Airdrops",
    description: "Pay influencers using Crypto, NFT or Airdrops",
    icon: "./okay.svg"
  }
]

export const profiles = [
  {
    name: "Mark Ray",
    position: "Founder and CEO",
    profile: "./profile/1.svg"
  },
  {
    name: "John Smith",
    position: "Co-founder and CFO",
    profile: "./profile/2.svg"
  },
  {
    name: "Lisa Lawrence",
    position: "Co-founder and CTO",
    profile: "./profile/3.svg"
  }
]

export const featureAccordionData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Uncover the Perfect Influencers",
    answer: "Efficiently discover influencers who align with your brand’s values",
    image: "./features/1.webp"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Seamless Connection and Collaboration",
    answer: "Effortlessly connect and collaborate with influencers",
    image: "./features/2.webp"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Efficiency and Effectiveness Reporting",
    answer: "Track & optimize the effectiveness of campaigns",
    image: "./features/3.webp"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Convenient Crypto Payments and Airdrops",
    answer: "Pay Influencers using Crypto, NFT or Airdrops",
    image: "./features/4.webp"
  }
]